clipjunkie.com 2014-06-29

# Contact Us at ClipJunkie.com

**ClipJunkie.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

**Personal Information**  
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

**Information Automatically Logged**  
Site name also logs IP addresses for systems administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user's session. This gives Site name an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a users session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous 

**Cookies**  
Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. Site name will only store information provided voluntarily, but this information is not personally identifiable. If for some reason you would rather not take advantage of the benefits made possible with cookies, most browsers allow you to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us here.
